# Keithellakpam Chourajit Singh

IMPHAL, IN 795001 9402692650 kc18singh@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Detail-oriented team player with a literature and research background with strong organizational skills. Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. To seek and maintain a full-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills.

## **Skills**

- Event planning and market research
- Active listening and strong communication
- Interpersonal skills and time management
- Analytical and critical thinking
- Content creation, editing and proofreading
- Remote teamwork, idea development and brainstorming
- Adaptability
- Decision making
- Creative problem-solving

# **Experience**

FEBRUARY 2023 - MARCH2023

#### Space Food Club - Mira-Bhayandar, Maharashtra - ONLINE INTERN

- Participated in online sessions discussing the basics of space. Explored the concepts and ideas related to space food.
- Completed a project by collaborating with different team members where we came up with a new dish for consumption in space by applying the concepts we learnt throughout the internship.

JULY 2022 - JANUARY 2023

## Vachana 2023, Christ University - Bengaluru, India - FINANCE COMMITTEE MEMBER

- Enhanced financial reporting accuracy by implementing and maintaining internal controls.
- Developed budget forecasts and participated in budget planning, ensuring alignment with organizational goals.
- Collaborated with other committee members to develop strategic plans.
- Ensured timely preparation of accurate financial statements for presentation to professors and administrative heads.
- Streamlined financial processes to improve efficiency and reduce operational costs.

## **Education**

2021 - 2023

Christ University - Bengaluru, India - Master of Arts English And Cultural Studies

2018 - 2021

St. Edmund's College - Shillong, India - Bachelor of Arts English Literature